The enemy's strategy is extremely simple.
They will use the shockwave from the landing castle impact as a clearing operation,
eliminating our forces and giving themselves a beachhead.
But for the past 15 years, we have been making plans to defend against it.
Our combined forces will surround and annihilate the enemy
before they can deploy any of their ground troops.
Make it so!
We'll be right back.
Undersea cables, Southern Cross Concerto 1, they're cut.
Miami landing station is silent.
And comm satellites!
Martian landing castle!
We have orbital attack!
UFE main and secondary command comms are down.
Alpha leader to squadron.
Commence attack on my lead.
What was that?
The squadron is gone.
Hold enemy position.
Silver 2-2.
They're jamming us.
Silver squad appears to have made contact with the enemy.
All units deploy!
Engage at will!
That's it!
Commander!
You sand primitives.
Bow down before the might of the gods.
Swear allegiance or be annihilated.
These are the only options left to you.
All right then.
How can this be happening?
Their cataphracts are too strong.
We can't beat these guys.
There's no way.
We are only insects to them.
As expected.
Pardon, my lord.
I think we should advance on Shinawara right away.
Planting our flag at the scene of her highness's tragic death.
Will only serve to solidify the righteousness of our cause.
Hmm.
That was my plan all along.
But even more so is that we secure the drop site.
Then Count Cruteo, please.
Allow me the honor of doing that for you.
An opportunity to repay your hospitality.
At least some.
Hmm.
The task is yours, Trillram.
Apprehend the area's leaders and ascertain the details surrounding the death of her highness.
Yes, sir.
Happening right now.
Moments ago it was confirmed that the world's major cities have come under attack by the imperial forces of Verse.
Due to a communications breakdown of unknown origin, the extent of damage in these cities is unclear.
Spokesperson say it is likely to attack.
There are more than enough seats available.
Everyone must please begin to board in an orderly manner.
Citizens of Shinawara City, an evacuation advisory is in effect.
Is there anyone here who has not left yet?
Not left yet.
Tell me.
Huh.
How exactly did we get roped into doing this?
Didn't have much of a choice.
They're really short-handed.
And I can't say no to Inko.
I'll take helping out the student council any day.
Wow, the fighting's really ramping up.
What do you think? Are we gonna get drafted?
That would suck.
Nah, you don't get drafted until after you graduate.
Maybe if the fighting drags on and there's a shortage of troops,
and they're really desperate or something.
Then they might.
Inko! Got another family out there! About 10 o'clock!
Seriously?
Damn Martians.
What?
Well, like I said, we got put on standby, so I can't just leave when I want to.
But I thought the plan was to leave town in your car, Yuki.
Wait a minute! Don't tell me you're still at our house!
Why didn't you evacuate with everyone else?
Oh, right. I could have done that.
You need to be more flexible.
Look at things and make the call! Go with your gut!
Isn't that what I say to you all the time?
Sure, Penivia.
What's that?
Never mind. I'll get a lift on one of the transports patrolling the area.
Be careful, okay?
Yeah, you too.
Excuse me.
You really shouldn't be here.
The government's been evacuating this whole area.
Are you guys tourists?
Do you speak a...
My apologies.
You do understand.
Yes. Thank you for your courtesy.
Meaning no disrespect, of course.
But while I have you like this, might I ask you a few questions?
Be my guest.
Why are you evacuating?
All of Tokyo has fallen. Because of the sudden attack by the Martians. It's not safe.
We must contact the proper authorities, so we can inform our people we are safe.
Your embassy, you mean? I don't think you'll find that they're open.
Since the assassination of the Mars Princess, the UFE is...
Princess Asalem is...
She is alive. She did not take part in the parade.
The unique gravity of Mars Princess is...
No, no, no.
The planet's not safe.
No, no, no, no.
No.
No, no, no.
The planet's not safe.
No, no, no, no.
parade the unique gravity of earth made her feel unwell her double died i understand how you feel
interesting if that's the case
help is on the way i texted the rescue transport our location you'll be safe there
slain troyard well well i didn't expect you to be my chauffeur on this little errand
sir the order came from my lord cruteo no doubt make certain i don't find you in my way terran scum
so glad you were here i can't believe that my car chose to run out of gas today
then i think you owe me one doctor well that goes for you too inaho
hey slacking off again over there okujo yeah but still
they russian european you think not shinoara standard i don't care about that a babe like
her is all right with me well done inaho you just scored a 10. thank you stupid boys
kg-7 arrayons wow what are you people doing here this area is supposed to be evacuated
that voice yuki is that you huh inko is nao in there with you too
oh what are you guys doing here hey if the cataphract squads mobilize is the enemy on their way to
shinawara yes high temp thermal signatures are headed this way this is a projected combat zone turn
around but we can't this is the way to the fairy pier do whatever it takes to find a safe place and
hunker down we'll try and hold them off we have no choice
enemy is approaching fighter squadron one o'clock well they seem to be very anxious to die
don't they all right first a warning
target locked amram squadron fire
confirm impact
enemy is attacked
filthy scum do it slain
oh no no no no no an appalling lack of training on this boy's part count cruteo
no matter allow me to educate you in the art of the battlefield
this terran is how it is done
it's begun message from hq fighter squadron has met an enemy aircraft
clearly engaging now what is it com's reception is messed up we're being jammed
they're using em pulses against our radio command channel
just like 15 years ago they like that trick
yeah like you were actually there you fraud
just to have
so
and
cause
Much more satisfying when they understand that their lives are over.
Tell me, Slain, just how does it feel to watch from up on high as your planet's people
die proving their uselessness?
Fighter Squadron is wiped out!
Enemy craft continuing towards Shinoara!
We gotta hurry.
There's our ride.
Yeah. And now we'll be returning home at last, there to be rewarded for the success of our good work.
Great honor and knighthood for us all.
This was a difficult time for you, wasn't it, Rae?
Not being with you, Father.
We're above the target.
Then set me down.
Yes. Neelokaris, disconnecting.
There he comes.
Baron Trilram, we have been waiting for your arrival.
Nice work. You've accomplished your mission very well.
Oh, my god. It's the light of Alt-Noah.
And now we say farewell. You were such good little rats.
But we really mustn't have you squeaking at an inopportune moment in the future, you see.
What have we here? Look at that beautiful little baby rat.
You can't escape me!
Enemy cataphract spotted! Bastard! It's going after a civilian!
Commence attack and we can make short work of him. Laser comms only. Firing position.
But, sir!
I set to attack! Fire!
Stop firing! We've got to rescue that civilian!
Our fire's not getting through!
Kaizuka, secure the survivor! I'm going to cover you!
Roger that!
Not are you?
Lieutenant Marito! This is my platoon!
You don't give orders here!
unsere data around here!
Mais amassant, we're still waiting for it.
And the enemy's going to be the home family!
What about the levity?
You can understand what's connection between the Kirk?
Where did we see him in the back?
We'll be on our seat, take care of them.
Tape!
Av centena!
They cannot be serious.
Now!
Get in!
Civilians secured!
Use grenades!
I told you to stop giving orders!
That thing's body is invulnerable to us!
Stay calm!
Let him have it!
Oh my god!
Meddlers dealt with.
Now back to my little rodent extermination.
Run, Kaija!
Good job!
No! Lieutenant!
Die with valor or die with cowardice.
Cowardice!
You think you're making some noble choice here?
Ahhhh!
Hm. Such a pity.
Marito, look out!
Headquarters! Come in! Headquarters!
Is it just me or are we getting nowhere fast?
Well, what else could we do?
This is warrants, officer 12-class!
The appointment!
Yuki!
Get this girl in the vehicle and get out of here!
Yuki! Wait a minute!
What's happening?
Hurry!
Sergeant!
No, wait!
No more trouble out of you, little rat!
Aiko! Step on the gas!
I am!
He's catching up to us!
We're too heavy!
Brakes!
Slam on the brakes!
Come again?
Hurry!
Hit the brakes!
Now gas it!
Right!
Let's go!
Would you just stand still?
Uncle Joe, wait!
Yuki's out there! We've gotta help her!
It's too dangerous!
I'm sorry!
I'm alright!
Now leave him in the dust!
Dust!
Inouho!
Oh...
Do we need a little hand?
Okisuke...
Too much time playing.
You were great.
Hey, we're safe now, you two! He's not following us any...
Hey, Inaho. Where's Okojo?
Oh, please, no.
Morning, Kaisuke. This is Morito. Do you copy?
Extractor Morito...
Kaisuke!
Listen close. That Martian is following you. He hasn't attacked a fairy yet.
Draw him away as best you can. But don't be a hero! You come back, got it?
Inaho?
He says that Martian cataphract is still following us. And that we could buy some time for the refugees who are leaving on the ferry if we're willing to be a decoy.
Whoa! What are you saying?
Utility tunnels can get us to the school.
And then what are we supposed to do?
There are training units in the hangar. And live ammunition that we can use.
Are you serious?
Let's fight it. Yuki and the others have tried. Now it's our turn too.
Let's fight that Martian cataphract.
Let's fight it.
Alright.
okay.
we've got
Higher
Oh
I pray for one